<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<!DOCTYPE doc SYSTEM "djnml-1.0b.dtd">
<doc msize="000003600" md5="88126f4485d50de58a364d02a3045d8d" sysId="sbknwsarchp01" destination="AW" distId="    " transmission-date="                " >
<djnml publisher="DJN" docdate="20150313" product="DN" seq="253" xml:lang="en-us" >
<head>
<copyright year="2015" holder="Dow Jones &amp; Company, Inc." ></copyright>
<docdata>
<djn>
<djn-newswires news-source="DJDN" origin="DJ" service-id="CO" >
<djn-press-cutout/>
<djn-urgency>0</djn-urgency>
<djn-mdata brand="DJ" temp-perm="P" retention="N" hot="N" original-source="FW" accession-number="20150313000253" page-citation="" display-date="20150313T050350.513Z" >
<djn-coding>
<djn-industry>
<c>I/NZDUS</c>
</djn-industry>
<djn-page>
<c>1062</c>
<c>20711</c>
<c>4171</c>
</djn-page>
<djn-subject>
<c>N/AER</c>
<c>N/BKG</c>
<c>N/CMDI</c>
<c>N/CMR</c>
<c>N/DJAE</c>
<c>N/DJAN</c>
<c>N/DJG</c>
<c>N/DJGP</c>
<c>N/DJGS</c>
<c>N/DJGV</c>
<c>N/DJI</c>
<c>N/DJIB</c>
<c>N/DJIV</c>
<c>N/DJMB</c>
<c>N/DJMS</c>
<c>N/DJN</c>
<c>N/DJRT</c>
<c>N/DN</c>
<c>N/EMR</c>
<c>N/EWR</c>
<c>N/FNVW</c>
<c>N/FXW</c>
<c>N/MADN</c>
<c>N/WED</c>
<c>N/WER</c>
<c>N/APIN</c>
<c>N/BON</c>
<c>N/DJFN</c>
<c>N/DJWI</c>
<c>N/FCTV</c>
<c>N/FRX</c>
<c>N/FXC</c>
<c>N/FXTR</c>
<c>N/MFO</c>
<c>N/MKC</c>
<c>N/MKT</c>
<c>N/TSY</c>
</djn-subject>
<djn-market>
<c>M/NND</c>
<c>M/NZD</c>
<c>M/TPX</c>
</djn-market>
<djn-product>
<c>P/FXTR</c>
<c>P/AEQ</c>
<c>P/AEQI</c>
<c>P/AFXB</c>
<c>P/AFXI</c>
<c>P/AFXP</c>
<c>P/EMG</c>
<c>P/FNVW</c>
<c>P/MAAD</c>
<c>P/RCC</c>
<c>P/WMMI</c>
</djn-product>
<djn-geo>
<c>R/ASI</c>
<c>R/FE</c>
<c>R/NZ</c>
<c>R/PRM</c>
</djn-geo>
</djn-coding>
</djn-mdata>
</djn-newswires>
</djn>
</docdata>
</head>
<body>
<headline brand-display="DJ" >
New Zealand Dollar Stronger, Helped By RBNZ Comments on Economy</headline>
<text>
<pre>
 
   By Rebecca Howard 
 </pre>
<p>
  WELLINGTON, New Zealand--The New Zealand dollar was stronger late Friday, still benefiting from comments from the central bank earlier in the week and a softer U.S. dollar. </p>
<p>
  In late Wellington trading, the New Zealand dollar was at US$0.7375 versus US$0.7303 late Wednesday and was at A$0.9606 compared with A$0.9621. </p>
<p>
  The Kiwi is holding firm, still benefiting from comments Thursday from the central bank governor on the strength of the New Zealand economy, said ANZ&apos;s senior forex manager, Sam Tuck. </p>
<p>
  He said the other main driver for the Kiwi was the U.S. dollar, which fell  after last night&apos;s weak retail sales data lead to some profit taking on the greenback, in particular given the dollar index is up 4% over March. </p>
<p>
  &quot;We are still relatively happy with the U.S. dollar bull trend. We could pull back a little bit more and not break that trend. I still believe the direction is dollar strength,&quot; he said. </p>
<p>
  He said the markets will be closely focused on three things next week: the U.S. Federal Open Market Committee meeting, domestic data including the fourth-quarter gross domestic product and balance of payments numbers as well as other indicators such as consumer confidence, and finally the GlobalDairyTrade auction. </p>
<p>
  &quot;With dairy futures down 15% since the last auction (two weeks ago) and the threat to our industry from the 1080 persons, we will be watching with great interest,&quot; he said. </p>
<p>
  The New Zealand government raised security and testing earlier this week after an anonymous threat was made to contaminate dairy baby formula and other formulas with pest control poison sodium fluoroacetate, otherwise known as 1080. </p>
<pre>
 </pre>
<p>
  Write to Rebecca Howard at rebecca.howard@wsj.com </p>
<pre>
 </pre>
<p>
  (END) Dow Jones Newswires</p>
<p>
  March 13, 2015 01:03 ET (05:03 GMT)</p>
</text>
</body>
</djnml>
</doc>
